export const Questions = [
  {
    prompt: "How can you measure the efficiency of an the algorithm?",
    optionA: "Processor and Memory",
    optionB: "Complexity and Capacity",
    optionC: "Time and Space",
    optionD: "Data and Space",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "How can we measure the time factor when determining the efficiency of the algorithm?",
    optionA: "Counting microseconds",
    optionB: "Counting the number of key operations",
    optionC: "Counting the number of statements",
    optionD: "Counting the kilobytes of algorithm",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "The complexity theory does not contain the following case, which is?",
    optionA: "Best Case",
    optionB: "Worse Case",
    optionC: "Average Case",
    optionD: "Null Case",
    answer: "D",
  },
  //   {
  //     prompt: "The Average case occurs in the linear search algorithm.",
  //     optionA: "When Item is somewhere in the middle of the array",
  //     optionB: "When Item is not in the array at all",
  //     optionC: "When Item is the last element in the array",
  //     optionD:
  //       "When Item is the last element in the array or is not there at all",
  //     answer: "A",
  //   },
  //   {
  //     prompt: "The complexity of the linear search algorithm is",
  //     optionA: "O(n)",
  //     optionB: "O(log n)",
  //     optionC: "O(n^2)",
  //     optionD: "O(n log n)",
  //     answer: "A",
  //   },
  //   {
  //     prompt: "The complexity of the Binary search algorithm is",
  //     optionA: "O(n)",
  //     optionB: "O(log)",
  //     optionC: "O(n^2)",
  //     optionD: "O(n log n) ",
  //     answer: "B",
  //   },
  //   {
  //     prompt: "The complexity of the Bubble sort algorithm is",
  //     optionA: "O(n)",
  //     optionB: "O(log)",
  //     optionC: "O(n^2)",
  //     optionD: "O(n log n) ",
  //     answer: "C",
  //   },
  //   {
  //     prompt: "The complexity of the merge sort algorithm is",
  //     optionA: "O(n)",
  //     optionB: "O(log)",
  //     optionC: "O(n^2)",
  //     optionD: "O(n log n) ",
  //     answer: "D",
  //   },
  //   {
  //     prompt:
  //       "Can you guess which of the following data structure is NOT a linear data structure?",
  //     optionA: "Arrays",
  //     optionB: "Linked List",
  //     optionC: "Both of the Above",
  //     optionD: "None of the Above",
  //     answer: "D",
  //   },
  //   {
  //     prompt:
  //       "Can you guess which of the following data structure is linear data structure?",
  //     optionA: "Trees",
  //     optionB: "Graphs",
  //     optionC: "Arrays",
  //     optionD: "None of the Above",
  //     answer: "C",
  //   },
  //   {
  //     prompt:
  //       "Which function findings the location of the element with a given value is:",
  //     optionA: "Traversal",
  //     optionB: "Search",
  //     optionC: "Sort",
  //     optionD: "None of the Above",
  //     answer: "B",
  //   },
  //   {
  //     prompt: "Arrays are the best data structures",
  //     optionA: "For relatively permanent collections of data",
  //     optionB:
  //       "For the size of the structure and the data in the structure are constantly changing",
  //     optionC: "For both of the above situation",
  //     optionD: "For none of the above situation",
  //     answer: "A",
  //   },
  //   {
  //     prompt: "Linked lists are the best suited",
  //     optionA: "For relatively permanent collections of data",
  //     optionB:
  //       "For the size of the structure and the data in the structure are constantly changing",
  //     optionC: "For both of the above situation",
  //     optionD: "For none of the above situation",
  //     answer: "B",
  //   },
  //   {
  //     prompt:
  //       "Each array declaration does not give, implicitly or explicitly, the information about which of the following?",
  //     optionA: "The name of the array",
  //     optionB: "The exact data type of array",
  //     optionC: "The first data from the set that will be stored",
  //     optionD: "Index set",
  //     answer: "C",
  //   },
  //   {
  //     prompt:
  //       "Why are the elements of an array are stored successively memory cells?",
  //     optionA:
  //       "In this way, the computer can keep track only the address of the first element, and the addresses of other elements can be calculated",
  //     optionB:
  //       "The architecture of computer memory does not allow arrays to store other than serially",
  //     optionC: "Both of above",
  //     optionD: "None of above",
  //     answer: "A",
  //   },
];
